Guide to the Bill Andrews Editorial Cartoons and Papers GRAPHICS.038
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series II: Finished Artwork
  - Finished Artwork, Sep 1976 (Box 21, Folder 305)
  - Finished Artwork, Sep 1976 (Flat-file-folder 2 Left)
  - Finished Artwork, Oct 8, 1976 (Flat-file-folder 2)
  - Finished Artwork, Oct 1976 (Box 21, Folder 306)
  - Finished Artwork, Nov 1976 (Box 21, Folder 307)
  - Finished Artwork, Dec 16, 1976 (Box Shared Tamiment 148, Folder 8)
  - Finished Artwork, Dec 1976 (Box 21, Folder 308)
  - Finished Artwork, 1976 (Box 11, Folder 243)
  - Finished Artwork, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 284)
  - Finished Artwork, Jan 1977 (Box 21, Folder 309)
  - Finished Artwork, Jan 1977 - Mar 1977 (Flat-file-folder 4 Left)
  - Finished Artwork, Jan 1977 - Mar 1977 (Flat-file-folder 2)
  - Finished Artwork, Feb 1977 (Box 21, Folder 310)
  - Finished Artwork, Mar 1977 (Box 22, Folder 311)
  - Finished Artwork, Apr 1977 (Box 22, Folder 312)
  - Finished Artwork, April 1977 - May 1977 (Flat-file-folder 5 Left)
  - Finished Artwork, Apr 1977 - May 1977 (Flat-file-folder 2)
  - Finished Artwork, May 1977 (Box 22, Folder 313)
  - Finished Artwork, Jun 1977 (Box 22, Folder 314)
  - Finished Artwork, June 1977 (Flat-file-folder 6 Right)
  - Finished Artwork, Jun 1977 (Flat-file-folder 2)
  - Finished Artwork, Jul 1977 (Box 22, Folder 315)
  - Finished Artwork, Jul 1977 (Flat-file-folder 7 Right)
  - Finished Artwork, Aug 1977 (Box 22, Folder 316)
  - Finished Artwork, Aug 1977 (Flat-file-folder 2)
  - Finished Artwork, Aug 1977 (Flat-file-folder 8 Right)
  - Finished Artwork, Sep 13, 1977 (Box 27, Folder 356)
  - Finished Artwork, Sep 1977 (Box 22, Folder 317)
  - Finished Artwork, Sep 1977 - Oct 1977 (Flat-file-folder 9 Right)
  - Finished Artwork, Oct 1977 (Box 22, Folder 318)
  - Finished Artwork, 1977 (Box 22, Folder 319)
  - Finished Artwork, 1977 (Flat-file-folder 2)
  - Finished Artwork, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 244)
  - Finished Artwork, 1978 (Box 18, Folder 285)
  - Finished Artwork, Jan 5, 1979 (Box 27, Folder 357)
  - Finished Artwork, Jun 18, 1980 (Box 23, Folder 321)
  - Finished Artwork, Jun 26, 1980 (Box 23, Folder 322)
  - Finished Artwork, Jun 1980 (Box 27, Folder 358)
  - Finished Artwork, Jul 1, 1980 (Box 23, Folder 323)
  - Finished Artwork, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 245)
  - Finished Artwork, 1980 (Box 18, Folder 286)
  - Finished Artwork, 1980 (Box 22, Folder 320)
  - Finished Artwork, Feb 1981 (Box 23, Folder 324)
  - Finished Artwork, Feb 1986 (Box 23, Folder 325)
  - Finished Artwork, undated (Box 12, Folder 246)
  - Finished Artwork, undated (Box 12, Folder 247)
  - Finished Artwork, undated (Box 18, Folder 287)
  - Finished Artwork, undated (Box 23, Folder 326)
  - Finished Artwork, undated (Box 27, Folder 359)
  - Finished Artwork, undated (Flat-file-folder 10 Right)
  - Finished Artwork, undated (Flat-file-folder 2)
  - Finished Artwork: Arizona State University, undated (Box 12, Folder 248)
  - Finished Artwork: Arizona State University, undated (Box 12, Folder 249)
  - Finished Artwork: Arizona State University, undated (Box 12, Folder 251)
  - Finished Artwork: Arizona State University, undated (Box 12, Folder 252)
  - Finished Artwork: Arizona State University, undated (Box 13, Folder 253)
  - Finished Artwork: Arizona State University, undated (Box 13, Folder 254)
  - Finished Artwork: Arizona State University, undated (Box 18, Folder 288)
  - Finished Artwork: Arizona State University, undated (Box 23, Folder 327)
  - Subseries A: Comic Strips
    Contains the final versions of comic strips created by Andrews while he worked as a staff cartoonist at the Daily World before they were screened and sized for publication. These include Dick Tricky, a multi-page series that had a very short run; Is This the Way it Was?, a weekly strip which provides commentary on a number of (often unrelated) news items; Nix!, a weekly strip that responds to the activities and statements of President Richard M. Nixon and his administration; The Optic Nerve, a long-running weekly strip which deals with more general news topics; The World at Weakend, a weekly strip on general news topic that appeared on Saturdays; and Which Way Wuzzit?, a weekly strip similar in form and content to Is This the Way it Was?.
    - Dick Tricky, 1971-1972 (Box 27, Folder 360)
    - Is This the Way it Was?, Oct 1968- Dec 1968 (Box 27, Folder 362)
    - Is This the Way it Was?, Jan 1969- Apr 1969 (Box 27, Folder 363)
    - Is This the Way it Was?, May 1969- Aug 1969 (Box 28, Folder 364)
    - Is This the Way it Was?, Sep 1969- Dec 1969 (Box 28, Folder 365)
    - Is This the Way it Was?, Jan 1970 - Apr 1970 (Box 28, Folder 366)
    - Is This the Way it Was?, May 1970 - Aug 1970 (Box 28, Folder 367)
    - Is This the Way it Was?, Sep 1970 - Dec 1970 (Box 28, Folder 368)
    - Is This the Way it Was?, Jan 1971 - May 1971 (Box 28, Folder 369)
    - Is This the Way it Was?, Jun 1971 - Sep 1971 (Box 29, Folder 370)
    - Nix!, Jul 1970 - Dec 1970 (Box 29, Folder 371)
    - Nix!, Jan 1971 - Jun 1971 (Box 29, Folder 372)
    - Nix!, Jul 1971 - Dec 1971 (Box 29, Folder 373)
    - Nix!, Jan 1972 - Jun 1972 (Box 29, Folder 374)
    - Nix!, Jul 1972 - Dec 1972 (Box 29, Folder 375)
    - Nix!, Jan 1973, undated (Box 29, Folder 376)
    - The Optic Nerve, Jan 1973 - Jun 1973 (Box 29, Folder 377)
    - The Optic Nerve, Jul 1973 - Dec 1973 (Box 29, Folder 378)
    - The Optic Nerve, Jan 1974 - Feb 1974 (Box 30, Folder 379)
    - The Optic Nerve, Mar 1974 - May 1974 (Box 30, Folder 380)
    - The Optic Nerve, Jun 1974 - Dec 1974 (Box 30, Folder 381)
    - The Optic Nerve, 1974-1975 (Flat-file-folder 4)
    - The Optic Nerve, Jan 1974 - Dec 1974 (Flat-file-folder 1, Tray 3)
    - The Optic Nerve, Jan 1975 - Sep 1975 (Flat-file-folder 2, Tray 3)
    - The Optic Nerve, Oct 1975 - Dec 1975 (Flat-file-folder 1 Left)
    - The Optic Nerve, Jan 1976 - Feb 1976 (Flat-file-folder 4)
    - The Optic Nerve, Mar 1976 (Flat-file-folder 4)
    - The Optic Nerve, Apr 1976 (Flat-file-folder 3)
    - The Optic Nerve, May 1976 (Flat-file-folder 3)
    - The Optic Nerve, Jun 1976 (Flat-file-folder 3)
    - The Optic Nerve, Jul 1976 (Flat-file-folder 5)
    - The Optic Nerve, Aug 1976 (Flat-file-folder 5)
    - The Optic Nerve, Sep 1976 (Flat-file-folder 5)
    - The Optic Nerve, Sep 1976 - Dec 1976 (Box 30, Folder 381)
    - The Optic Nerve, Oct 1976-Nov 1976 (Flat-file-folder 4)
    - The Optic Nerve, Dec 1976 (Flat-file-folder 4)
    - The Optic Nerve, 1976 (Flat-file-folder 2 Left)
    - The Optic Nerve, Jan 1977 - May 1977 (Flat-file-folder 3 Left)
    - The Optic Nerve, Jan 1977 - Feb 1977 (Flat-file-folder 3)
    - The Optic Nerve, Mar 1977 - Apr 1977 (Flat-file-folder 3)
    - The Optic Nerve, May 1977 - Jun 1977 (Flat-file-folder 1)
    - The Optic Nerve, Jul 1977 - Aug 1977 (Flat-file-folder 1)
    - The Optic Nerve, Sep 1977 - Oct 1977 (Flat-file-folder 1)
    - The World at Weakend, Jan 1974 - Mar 1974 (Box 30, Folder 382)
    - The World at Weakend, Apr 1974 - Jun 1974 (Box 30, Folder 383)
    - The World at Weakend, Jun 1974 - Dec 1974 (Flat-file-folder 4 Left, Flat-file-folder 5 Left)
    - The World at Weakend, Jan 1975 - Oct 1975 (Flat-file-folder 6 Right, Flat-file-folder 7 Right)
    - Which Way Wuzzit?, Sep 1971 - Dec 1971 (Box 30, Folder 384)
    - Which Way Wuzzit?, Jan 1972 - Apr 1972 (Box 30, Folder 385)
    - Which Way Wuzzit?, May 1972 - Aug 1972 (Box 30, Folder 386)
    - Which Way Wuzzit?, Sep 1972 - Dec 1972 (Box 30, Folder 387)
    - Which Way Wuzzit?, May 1973 - Aug 1973 (Box 31, Folder 389)
    - Which Way Wuzzit?, Sep 1973 - Dec 1973 (Box 31, Folder 390)
    - Which Way Wuzzit?, Jan 1974 (Box 31, Folder 391)
- Series III: Pre Press Prints
  Contains the screened and sized versions of Andrews' artwork as prepared for publication. These materials are often touched up in order to achieve the Andrews' desired level of contrast and contrast. Prints he felts were unacceptable were placed in a folder titled "Unusable". Full-size versions of almost all of these prints can be found in the Finished Artwork series of this collection.
  Almost all of this material dates from the time that Andrews was employed at the Daily World, and responds to current events from the perspective of the Daily World and the Communist Party of the United States of America.
  A very small amount of material was created during the time that Andrews worked for Arizona State University, mostly for sizing purposes.
  - Pre Press Prints, 1965 (Box 23, Folder 523)
  - Pre Press Prints, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 443)
  - Pre Press Prints, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 444)
  - Pre Press Prints, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 445)
  - Pre Press Prints, Jan 1971 - Jun 1971 (Box 32, Folder 446)
  - Pre Press Prints, Jul 1971 - Dec 1971 (Box 32, Folder 447)
  - Pre Press Prints, 1971 (Box 13, Folder 516)
  - Pre Press Prints, Jan 1972 - Mar 1972 (Box 32, Folder 448)
  - Pre Press Prints, Apr 1972 - Jun 1972 (Box 32, Folder 449)
  - Pre Press Prints, Jul 1972 - Sep 1972 (Box 32, Folder 450)
  - Pre Press Prints, Oct 1972 - Dec 1972 (Box 32, Folder 451)
  - Pre Press Prints, Jan 1973 - Mar 1973 (Box 32, Folder 452)
  - Pre Press Prints, Apr 1973 - Jun 1973 (Box 32, Folder 453)
  - Pre Press Prints, Jul 1973 - Sep 1973 (Box 32, Folder 454)
  - Pre Press Prints, Oct 1973 - Dec 1973 (Box 32, Folder 455)
  - Pre Press Prints, 1973 (Box 13, Folder 517)
  - Pre Press Prints, Jan 1974 - Mar 1974 (Box 32, Folder 456)
  - Pre Press Prints, Apr 1974 - Jun 1974 (Box 32, Folder 457)
  - Pre Press Prints, Jul 1974 - Aug 1974 (Box 32, Folder 458)
  - Pre Press Prints, Sep 1974 - Oct 1974 (Box 32, Folder 459)
  - Pre Press Prints, Nov 1974 - Dec 1974 (Box 32, Folder 460)
  - Pre Press Prints, 1974 (Box 13, Folder 518)
  - Pre Press Prints, Jan 1975 - Feb 1975 (Box 32, Folder 461)
  - Pre Press Prints, Apr 1975 - Jun 1975 (Box 32, Folder 462)
  - Pre Press Prints, Aug 1975 - Oct 1975 (Box 32, Folder 463)
  - Pre Press Prints, Sep 1975 - Dec 1975 (Box 32, Folder 464)
  - Pre Press Prints, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 519)
  - Pre Press Prints, Jan 1976 - Feb 1976 (Box 32, Folder 465)
  - Pre Press Prints, Mar 1976 - Apr 1976 (Box 33, Folder 466)
  - Pre Press Prints, May 1976 - Jun 1976 (Box 33, Folder 467)
  - Pre Press Prints, Jul 1976 - Aug 1976 (Box 33, Folder 468)
  - Pre Press Prints, Sep 1976 (Box 33, Folder 469)
  - Pre Press Prints, Oct 1976 - Dec 1976 (Box 33, Folder 470)
  - Pre Press Prints, 1976 (Box 13, Folder 520)
  - Pre Press Prints, Jan 1977 - Feb 1977 (Box 33, Folder 471)
  - Pre Press Prints, Mar 1977 - Apr 1977 (Box 33, Folder 472)
  - Pre Press Prints, May 1977 - Jun 1977 (Box 33, Folder 473)
  - Pre Press Prints, Jul 1977 - Aug 1977 (Box 33, Folder 474)
  - Pre Press Prints, Sep 1977 - Oct 1977 (Box 33, Folder 475)
  - Pre Press Prints, 1977 (Box 13, Folder 521)
  - Pre Press Prints, 1977 (Box 23, Folder 524)
  - Pre Press Prints, 1980 (Box 33, Folder 476)
  - Pre Press Prints, undated (Box 33, Folder 477)
  - Pre Press Prints, undated (Box 13, Folder 522)
  - Pre Press Prints: Arizona State University, undated (Box 23, Folder 525)
  - Pre Press Prints: Unusable, 1977 (Box 33, Folder 478)
  - Subseries A: Comic Strips
    Contains the screened and sized versions of comic strips created by Andrews while he worked as a staff cartoonist at the Daily World. These include Dick Tricky, a multi-page series that had a very short run; Is This the Way it Was?, a weekly strip which provides commentary on a number of (often unrelated) news items; Nix!, a weekly strip that responds to the activities and statements of President Richard M. Nixon and his administration; The Optic Nerve, a long-running weekly strip which deals with more general news topics; The World at Weakend, a weekly strip on general news topic that appeared on Saturdays; and Which Way Wuzzit?, a weekly strip similar in form and content to Is This the Way it Was?.
    - Is This the Way it Was?, 1968 (Box 33, Folder 479)
    - Is This the Way it Was?, Jan 1969 - Jun 1969 (Box 33, Folder 480)
    - Is This the Way it Was?, Jul 1969 - Dec 1969 (Box 33, Folder 481)
    - Is This the Way it Was?, Jan 1970 - Jun 1970 (Box 33, Folder 482)
    - Is This the Way it Was?, Jul 1970 - Dec 1970 (Box 33, Folder 483)
    - Is This the Way it Was?, 1971 (Box 33, Folder 484)
    - Is This the Way it Was?, undated (Box 33, Folder 485)
    - Nix!, Jun 1970 - Dec 1970 (Box 33, Folder 486)
    - Nix!, Jan 1971 - Jun 1971 (Box 33, Folder 487)
    - Nix!, Jul 1971 - Dec 1971 (Box 33, Folder 488)
    - Nix!, Jan 1972 - Jun 1972 (Box 33, Folder 489)
    - Nix!, Jul 1972 - Dec 1972 (Box 33, Folder 490)
    - Nix!, Jan 1973 (Box 33, Folder 491)
    - The Optic Nerve, 1973 (Box 33, Folder 492)
    - The Optic Nerve, Jan 1974 - Jun 1974 (Box 33, Folder 493)
    - The Optic Nerve, Sep 1974 - Dec 1974 (Box 33, Folder 494)
    - The Optic Nerve, Jan 1975 (Box 33, Folder 495)
    - The Optic Nerve, Apr 1975 - Jun 1975 (Box 33, Folder 496)
    - The Optic Nerve, Aug 1975 - Dec 1975 (Box 33, Folder 497)
    - The Optic Nerve, Jan 1976 - Apr 1976 (Box 33, Folder 498)
    - The Optic Nerve, May 1976 - Sep 1976 (Box 34, Folder 499)
    - The Optic Nerve, Oct 1976 - Dec 1976 (Box 34, Folder 500)
    - The Optic Nerve, Jan 1977 - Jun 1977 (Box 34, Folder 501)
    - The Optic Nerve, Jul 1977 - Oct 1977 (Box 34, Folder 502)
    - The Optic Nerve, undated (Box 34, Folder 503)
    - The World at Weakend, Jan 1974 - Jun 1974 (Box 34, Folder 504)
    - The World at Weakend, Aug 1974 - Dec 1974 (Box 34, Folder 505)
    - The World at Weakend, Jan 1975 - Feb 1975 (Box 34, Folder 506)
    - The World at Weakend, Apr 1975 - Jun 1975 (Box 34, Folder 507)
    - The World at Weakend, Aug 1975 - Dec 1975 (Box 34, Folder 508)
    - Which Way Wuzzit?, 1971 (Box 34, Folder 509)
    - Which Way Wuzzit?, Jan 1972 - Jun 1972 (Box 34, Folder 510)
    - Which Way Wuzzit?, Jul 1972 - Dec 1972 (Box 34, Folder 511)
    - Which Way Wuzzit?, 1973 (Box 34, Folder 512)
    - Which Way Wuzzit?, Jan 1974 (Box 34, Folder 513)
    - Which Way Wuzzit?, undated (Box 34, Folder 514)
- Series IV: Subject Files
  Contains clippings, correspondence, clippings of Andrews' published artwork, typescripts and topical files assembled by Andrews. Of particular significance are typescripts of Andrews' talks describing his creative process as well as the editorial processes of the Daily World, leaflets and flyers he collected during the 1960s and 1970s, typescripts of articles (including musical album and concert reviews), and materials from his March 1977 trip to Moscow to participate in the Satire in the Struggle for Peace Exhibition. A folder containing photographs of Andrews is also present in the collection. The series also contains an oral history interview with Andrews, taken following the processing of the collection.
  - American Institute for Marxist Studies, 1965-1966 (Box 34, Folder 525)
  - Arizona Educationa Media Association: Arizona Media (magazine), 1980 (Box 34, Folder 526)
  - Arizona State University: Brochures and Pamphlets, 1982-1985, undated (Box 34, Folder 527)
  - Arizona State University: Brochures and Pamphlets, undated (Box 34, Folder 528)
  - Arizona State University: Flyers and Leaflets, 1984-1985, undated (Box 34, Folder 529)
  - Arizona State University: Graphics Department Annual Report, Jun 2, 1978 (Box 34, Folder 530)
  - Arizona State University: Periodicals, 1979, 1984 (Box 34, Folder 531)
  - Artists United, 1970, undated (Box 34, Folder 532)
  - Assembly of Unrepresented People (Washington, D.C.), Aug 1965 (Box 34, Folder 533)
  - Association of American Editorial Cartoonists, 1972-1977 (Box 34, Folder 534)
  - Biographical, 1969-2009 (Box 34, Folder 535)
  - Cartoon Contests and Awards, 1972-1977 (Box 34, Folder 536)
  - Central Arizona Film Cooperative: Newsletters, 1978-1979 (Box 34, Folder 537)
  - Citizen's Committee for Constitutional Liberties, undated (Box 34, Folder 538)
  - Clergymen's Emergency Committee for Vietnam, 1965 (Box 34, Folder 539)
  - Clippings, 1937-1939 (Box 31, Folder 627)
  - Clippings, 1961-1994 (Box 31, Folder 628)
  - Clippings, 1965-1975 (Box 34, Folder 540)
  - Clippings: Cartoons by Bill Day, 1975-1976 (Box 34, Folder 541)
  - Clippings: Cartoons by Dave Simpson, undated (Box 34, Folder 542)
  - Clippings: Cartoons by Don Wright, 1972-1976 (Box 34, Folder 543)
  - Clippings: Cartoons by Doug Marlette, 1976-1977 (Box 34, Folder 544)
  - Clippings: Cartoons by Gee Tee Maxwell, undated (Box 34, Folder 545)
  - Clippings: Cartoons by Jeff MacNelly (I), 1975-1976 (Box 34, Folder 546)
  - Clippings: Cartoons by Jeff MacNelly (II), 1975-1976 (Box 34, Folder 547)
  - Clippings: Cartoons by Ollie Harrington, 1977 (Box 34, Folder 548)
  - Clippings: Cartoons by Others, 1966, 1971-1976, undated (Box 34, Folder 549)
  - Clippings: Cartoons by Others, undated (Box 31, Folder 629)
  - Clippings: Cartoons by Pat Oliphant, 1975-1976 (Box 34, Folder 550)
  - Clippings: Cartoons by Tom Darcy, undated (Box 35, Folder 551)
  - Clippings: Cartoons by Tony Auth, 1975-1976 (Box 35, Folder 552)
  - Communist Party of the United States of America (CPUSA), 1970-1976 (Box 35, Folder 553)
  - Communist Party of the United States of America (CPUSA): Hall-Tyner Campaign, 1972 (Box 35, Folder 554)
  - Correspondence: Incoming, 1954-1957 (Box 35, Folder 555)
  - Correspondence: Incoming, 1963-1967 (Box 35, Folder 556)
  - Correspondence: Incoming, 1971-1974 (Box 35, Folder 557)
  - Correspondence: Incoming, 1975-1977 (Box 35, Folder 558)
  - Correspondence: Incoming, undated (Box 35, Folder 559)
  - Correspondence: Incoming: Crowell, Van, 1976-1977 (Box 35, Folder 560)
  - Correspondence: Incoming: Jacobs, Leo I. (Charles T. Branford Publishing Company), 1954 (Box 35, Folder 561)
  - Correspondence: Incoming: Paskow, Al, 1954, 1957 (Box 35, Folder 562)
  - Correspondence: Incoming: Richard, T. J., 1954-1957 (Box 35, Folder 563)
  - Correspondence: Outgoing, 1956-1957 (Box 35, Folder 564)
  - Correspondence: Outgoing, 1963-1968 (Box 35, Folder 565)
  - Correspondence: Outgoing, 1971-1977 (Box 35, Folder 566)
  - Current Projects, 1975-1976, undated (Box 35, Folder 567)
  - Daily World, 1972-1974 (Box 35, Folder 568)
  - Downtown CORE, 1965 (Box 35, Folder 569)
  - Financial, 1965-1974 (Box 35, Folder 570)
  - Fort Hood Three Defense Committee, 1966, undated (Box 35, Folder 571)
  - Fred Ellis: Daily World Tribute, 1973 (Box 35, Folder 572)
  - Graphic Arts Workshop, Mar 3, 1976 (Box 35, Folder 573)
  - House Internal Security Committee, 1971 (Box 35, Folder 574)
  - Housing, 1977 (Box 35, Folder 575)
  - International Publishers Associates, 1965 (Box 35, Folder 576)
  - Landlord, 1970-1976 (Box 35, Folder 577)
  - Leaflets and Pamphlets, 1967-1986 (Box 35, Folder 578)
  - Lower East Side Mobilization for Peace (LEMPA), 1966 (Box 35, Folder 579)
  - May Day Demonstrations, 1966, 1969 (Box 35, Folder 580)
  - Middle East, 1973-1974 (Box 35, Folder 581)
  - New World Review (journal), 1961-1964 (Box 35, Folder 582)
  - New World Review (journal): Essay Contest, 1961 (Box 35, Folder 583)
  - New World Review (journal): Essay Contest, 1962 (Box 35, Folder 584)
  - Noise, 1976-1977 (Box 35, Folder 585)
  - Notes, undated (Box 35, Folder 586)
  - Oral History Interview, Dec 5, 2011 and Dec 7, 2011 (Box 41, Folder 626.1)
    This oral history of Bill Andrews on DVD was taken via Skype by Hillel Arnold over two sessions in 2011, following Arnold's work processing the collection.
  - Phoenix Union High School: Class Assignments and Clippings, 1952-1954 (Box 35, Folder 587)
  - Photographs of Bill Andrews, 1969-2009, undated (Box 35, Folder 588)
  - Published Artwork: Cartoons for Arizona State University, 1980-1986, undated (Box 31, Folder 630)
  - Published Artwork: Cartoons for Arizona State University, undated (Box 35, Folder 589)
  - Published Artwork: Cartoons from Arizona Republic (sample from discarded scrapbook), 1956 (Box 35, Folder 590)
  - Published Artwork: Cartoons from Daily World, 1972-1977 (Box 35, Folder 591)
  - Published Artwork: Cartoons from Daily World, undated (Box 31, Folder 631)
  - Published Artwork: Cartoons from Daily World: Is This the Way it Was? (sample from discarded scrapbook), undated (Box 35, Folder 592)
  - Published Artwork: Cartoons from Daily World: The Optic Nerve, 1973-1976 (Box 35, Folder 593)
  - Published Artwork: Cartoons from Daily World: Which Way Wuzzit?, 1972-1975 (Box 35, Folder 594)
  - Published Artwork: Cartoons from Głos Ludowy (The People's Voice), 1971, 1974 (Box 35, Folder 595)
  - Published Artwork: Cartoons from Muhammad Speaks, 1971-1973 (Box 35, Folder 596)
  - Published Artwork: Cartoons in Foreign Papers, 1967-1975 (Box 35, Folder 597)
  - Published Artwork: Cartoons in Steel Labor (United Steel Workers), Apr 1972 (Box 35, Folder 598)
  - Published Artwork: Leaflets and Pamphlets, 1978-1986, undated (Box 35, Folder 599)
  - Satire in the Struggle for Peace Exhibition (Moscow): Certificate, Mar 1977 (Box 35, Folder 600)
  - Satire in the Struggle for Peace Exhibition (Moscow): Guidebooks, Mar 1977 (Box 35, Folder 601)
  - Satire in the Struggle for Peace Exhibition (Moscow): Notebooks, Mar 1977 (Box 35, Folder 602)
  - Satire in the Struggle for Peace Exhibition (Moscow): Travel Documents, Mar 1977 (Box 35, Folder 603)
  - Slides, undated (Box 35, Folder 604)
  - Southwest Regional English Teacher's Conference, Oct 1982 (Box 35, Folder 605)
  - Student Socialist Union, undated (Box 35, Folder 606)
  - Talks: Early Jazz, 1974 (Box 35, Folder 607)
  - Talks: Editorial Art, 1977 (Box 35, Folder 608)
  - Talks: How Cartoonists View Human Rights, 1977 (Box 35, Folder 609)
  - Talks: United States Bicentennial and the Working Class, 1976 (Box 36, Folder 611)
  - Technical Approaches to Cartooning, 1961-1973, undated (Box 36, Folder 612)
  - The Worker Annual Press Conference: Notes, Jan 31, 1965 (Box 36, Folder 613)
  - The Worker: Subscription Drives, 1964-1966 (Box 36, Folder 614)
  - Theater, undated (Box 36, Folder 615)
  - Ticket Stubs, 1966, undated (Box 36, Folder 616)
  - To Be Done, 1974-1975 (Box 36, Folder 617)
  - Typescripts, 1968, 1974-1976 (Box 36, Folder 618)
  - Typescripts (I), undated (Box 36, Folder 619)
  - Typescripts (II), undated (Box 36, Folder 620)
  - Typescripts (III), undated (Box 36, Folder 621)
  - University and College Designers Association: Membership List, 1983, 1985 (Box 36, Folder 622)
  - Vietnam: Periodicals, 1969-1971 (Box 36, Folder 623)
  - World Fellowship Center (Conway, New Hampshire), 1965-1966 (Box 36, Folder 624)
  - W. E. B. Du Bois Club, 1965, undated (Box 36, Folder 625)
  - Youth Against War and Fascism, Apr 1966 (Box 36, Folder 626)
- Series V: Ephemera
  Contains ephemeral and three-dimensional objects, including Andrews' camera, awards, printing plates, a scrapbook from his high school years, and an armband from an April 1969 protest against the Vietnam War.
  - Camera with Bag and Two Lenses, undated (Box 38)
  - Page One Awards (Newspaper Guild of New York), 1972-1974 (Box 39)
  - Linoleum Printing Block, undated (Box 40)
  - Scrapbook, 1949-1956 (Box 41)
  - "33,000" Armband (from Vietnam War Protest), Apr 1969 (Box 42, Folder 632)
  - Printing Plate from Daily World, Mar 27, 1974 (Box Shared Tamiment 148, Folder 5)
  - Printing Plate from Daily World (I), May 7, 1977 (Box Shared Tamiment 148, Folder 6)
  - Printing Plate from Daily World (II), May 7, 1977 (Box Shared Tamiment 148, Folder 10)
  - Wooden Object (frame?), undated (Box 42, Folder 636)
- Series VI: Artwork by Others